{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346557319","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346557319"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" 0123c309-2d6f-47aa-b705-c15e9a154e0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346561721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346561721"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" 0123c309-2d6f-47aa-b705-c15e9a154e0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-I-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346565979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346565979"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" 0123c309-2d6f-47aa-b705-c15e9a154e0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-U-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346569017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346569017"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" 0123c309-2d6f-47aa-b705-c15e9a154e0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-E-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346572230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346572230"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" 0123c309-2d6f-47aa-b705-c15e9a154e0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346577987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346577987"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" 0123c309-2d6f-47aa-b705-c15e9a154e0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346587615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346587615"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346588047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346588047"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346588533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346588533"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346589174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346589174"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346592212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346592212"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346592305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346592305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346593158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346593158"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346593572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346593571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346594395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346594395"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346597396","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346597396"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" KWEYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346598439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346598439"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" AMEVALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346599132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346599132"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346599325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346599324"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346599898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346599898"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346600691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346600691"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346603697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346603697"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346603800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346603800"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346604563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346604563"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346605075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346605075"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346605268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346605268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346605941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346605940"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346608724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346608724"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346608947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346608947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346609649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346609649"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346612700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346612700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346612812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346612812"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346613495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346613495"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346613977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346613977"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346614790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346614790"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346617800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346617800"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346618432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346618432"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" PINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346619165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346619165"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346619877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346619877"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346620010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346620010"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346620853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346620853"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346623870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346623870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346624013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346624013"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346624725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346624725"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346625238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346625238"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346625961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346625961"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346629020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346629020"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346629453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346629453"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346629945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346629944"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346630067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346630067"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346630820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346630820"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346633839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346633839"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346633952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346633952"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346634705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346634705"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346635078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346635078"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346636161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346636160"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346638940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346638940"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346639414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346639413"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346640416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346640416"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346643305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346643305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346643438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346643438"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346644011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346644011"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346644274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346644274"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346644886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346644886"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346648173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346648173"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346648886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346648886"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346649419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346649418"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346649571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346649571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346650104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346650104"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346650237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346650237"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346650830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346650830"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346653862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346653862"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346653955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346653955"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346654668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346654668"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346655091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346655091"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346656044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346656044"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" ZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346659049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346659049"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346659382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346659382"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346660106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346660105"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346660174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346660174"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346661237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346661236"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346663404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346663404"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346663866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346663866"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346665439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346665439"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" NIIPENDAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346666571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346666571"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346669567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346669567"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346671309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346671309"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" UNAZIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346671782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346671782"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346672365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346672365"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346672658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346672658"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346673670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346673670"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346676415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346676414"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346676493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346676493"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" f7dbefd1-0af8-4561-a59a-b010efc3d04f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346688177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346688177"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346688609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346688609"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346689093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346689092"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346689735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346689735"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346692765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346692765"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346692857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346692857"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346693709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346693709"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346694123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346694123"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346694946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346694946"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346697937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346697936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" KWEYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346698980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346698980"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" AMEVALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346699674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346699673"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346699867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346699867"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346700441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346700441"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346701235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346701235"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346704235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346704235"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346704338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346704338"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346705101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346705101"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346705614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346705614"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346705807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346705807"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346706480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346706480"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346709242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346709242"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346709466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346709466"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346710169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346710169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346713177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346713177"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346713289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346713289"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346713972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346713972"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346714455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346714455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346715268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346715268"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346718275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346718275"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346718908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346718908"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" PINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346719640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346719640"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346720354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346720353"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346720487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346720487"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346721330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346721330"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346724314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346724314"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346724457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346724457"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346725170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346725170"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346725682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346725682"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346726404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346726404"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346729448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346729447"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346729880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346729880"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346730372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346730372"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346730495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346730494"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346731247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346731247"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346734283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346734283"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346734396","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346734396"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346735152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346735152"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346735525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346735525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346736608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346736608"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346739398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346739397"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346739870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346739870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346740873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346740873"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346743727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346743727"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346743860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346743860"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346744434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346744433"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346744696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346744696"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346745311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346745310"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346748592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346748592"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346749305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346749305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346749838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346749838"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346749991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346749991"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346750524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346750524"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346750657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346750657"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346751250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346751250"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346754279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346754279"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346754372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346754372"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346755085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346755085"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346755508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346755508"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346756462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346756462"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" ZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346759450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346759449"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346759782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346759782"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346760505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346760504"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346760568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346760568"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346761633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346761633"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346763823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346763823"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346764285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346764285"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346765857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346765857"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" NIIPENDAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346766990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346766990"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346769954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346769954"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346771698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346771698"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" UNAZIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346772172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346772172"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346772756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346772755"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346773048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346773048"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346774061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346774061"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346776787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346776787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346776841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346776841"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346783201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346783201"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346789933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346789932"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190124_191539"," gameId":" be93790f-4569-4ba0-be06-7c3b578cb723"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}